[ar:Taylor Swift]
[ti:Hey Stephen]
[by:royaldat_BA]


[00:04.25]uhhhhhhhhh..........eh

[00:19.85]hey stephen, i know looks can be deceiving but i know i saw a light in you
[00:28.04]as we walked we were talking and i didn’t say half the things i wanted to
[00:35.98]of all the girls tossing rocks at your window i’ll be the one waiting there even when it’s cold
[00:44.95]hey stephen, boy you might have me believing i don’t always have to be alone

chorus
[00:52.73]cause i can’t help it if you look like an angel
[00:56.82]can’t help it if i wanna kiss you in the rain so
[01:00.76]come feel this magic i’ve been feeling since i met you
[01:04.56]can’t help it if there’s no one else
[01:09.40]i can’t help myself

[01:19.67]hey stephen, i’ve been holding back this feeling so i’ve got some things to say to you
[01:27.90]i seen it all so i thought but i never seen nobody shine the way you do
[01:36.12]the way you walk the way you talk the way you say my name
[01:40.32]it’s beautiful, wonderful - don’t you ever change
[01:44.71]hey stephen, why are people always leaving i think you and i should stay the same

[01:52.89]cause i can’t help it if you look like an angel
[01:56.50]can’t help it if i wanna kiss you in the rain so
[02:00.66]come feel this magic i’ve been feeling since i met you
[02:04.46]can’t help it if there’s no one else
[02:09.27]i can’t help myself

[02:19.99]they’re dimming the street lights, you’re perfect for me why aren’t you here tonight
[02:27.80]i’m waiting alone now so come on and come out and pull me near
[02:35.28]shine, shine, shine

[02:40.46]hey stephen, i could give you fifty reasons why i should be the one you choose
[02:48.41]all those other girls, well they’re beautiful but would they write a song for you

[02:56.43]i can’t help it if you look like an angel
[03:00.69]can’t help it if i wanna kiss you in the rain so
[03:04.77]come feel this magic i’ve been feeling since i met you
[03:08.35]can’t help it if there’s no one else
[03:13.14]i can’t help myself

[03:16.33]if you look like an angel
[03:19.21]can’t help it if wanna kiss you in the rain so
[03:23.39]come feel this magic i’ve been feeling since i met you
[03:26.99]can’t help it if there’s no one else
[03:31.88]i can’t help myself
[03:38.78]myself, can’t help myself
[03:44.71]i can’t help myself 

[03:50.20]uhhhhhhhhh

