[ar:Taylor Swift]
[ti:The Best Day]
[by:royaldat_BA]


[00:17.95]I’m five years old
[00:20.14]It’s getting cold
[00:21.53]I’ve got
[00:23.15]A big coat on

[00:25.49]I hear your laugh
[00:27.51]And look up smiling at you
[00:30.25]And run and run

[00:32.62]At the pumpkin patch
[00:34.65]The tractor rolls on
[00:37.82]The sky is gold
[00:40.31]I hug your legs and fall asleep
[00:45.73]The whole way home

[00:48.32]I don’t know why all the trees change in the fall
[00:56.03]I know that you’re not scared of anything at all
[01:03.12]Don’t know if Snow White’s house is near or far away
[01:08.67]But I know that I had the best day
[01:12.29]With you today

[01:22.29]I’m thirteen now
[01:24.00]And don’t know how my friends
[01:27.37]Could be so mean

[01:29.68]I come crying
[01:32.59]You hold me tight
[01:34.87]And grab the keys

[01:37.21]And you drive and drive
[01:39.42]Until we’ve found a town
[01:42.20]Far enough away

[01:44.87]And we talk and window-shop
[01:47.89]Until I’ve forgotten all their names

[01:53.23]I don’t know who I’m gonna talk to
[01:58.01]Now at school
[02:00.67]I know I’m laughing on the car ride home with you
[02:07.79]Don’t know how long it’s gonna take to feel okay
[02:13.48]But I know I had the best day
[02:16.51]With you today

[02:23.18]I have an excellent father
[02:27.06]His strength is making me stronger
[02:30.36]God smiles on my little brother
[02:34.14]Inside and out
[02:35.65]He’s better than nothing

[02:38.25]I grew up in a pretty house
[02:42.48]And I had space to run
[02:45.50]And I had the best days with you

[02:53.65]There is a video
[02:56.42]I found from back when I was three
[03:01.01]You set up a paint set in the kitchen
[03:05.70]And you’re talking to me

[03:08.61]It’s the edge of princesses and pirate ships
[03:13.43]And the seven dwarves
[03:16.46]Daddy’s smart
[03:17.73]And you’re the prettiest lady in the whole wide world

[03:24.48]Now I know why all the trees change in the fall
[03:31.50]And you were on my side
[03:34.90]Even when I was wrong
[03:38.21]And I love you for giving me your eyes
[03:42.92]Staying back and watching me shine

[03:47.53]And I didn’t know if you knew
[03:49.42]So I’m taking this chance to say
[03:52.54]That I had the best day
[03:55.31]With you today 

