[ar:Taylor Swift]
[ti:Change]




[00:21.01]It's just a sad picture,
[00:23.57]The final blow hits you
[00:25.88]Somebody else gets what you wanted again
[00:30.94]You know it's all the same
[00:33.38]Another time and place
[00:35.94]Repeating history, and your getting sick of it
[00:40.22]
[00:40.66]But I believe in whatever you do
[00:44.84]And I'll do anything to see it through
[00:48.46]
[00:48.77]Because these things will change
[00:51.52]Can you feel it now?
[00:54.02]These walls that they put up to hold us back will fall down
[00:59.27]It's a revolution, the time will come for us to finally win
[01:09.05]We'll sing hallelujah
[01:14.24]We'll sing hallelujah
[01:21.87]
[01:23.18]So you've been outnumbered
[01:25.81]Raided and now cornered
[01:28.56]It's hard to fight when the fight ain't fair
[01:33.25]We're getting stronger now
[01:35.87]From things they never found
[01:38.37]They might be bigger, but we're faster and never scared
[01:43.31]You can walk away and say we don't need this
[01:47.72]But there's something in your eyes, says we can beat this
[01:50.98]
[01:51.54]These things will change
[01:54.04]Can you feel it now?
[01:56.48]These walls that they put up to hold us back will fall down
[02:01.66]It's a revolution, the time will come for us to finally win
[02:11.52]We'll sing hallelujah
[02:16.59]We'll sing hallelujah
[02:43.00]
[02:43.62]Tonight we're standing on our knees
[02:48.42]To fight for what we worked for all these years
[02:53.86]The battle was long, it's the fight of our lives
[02:58.55]Will we stand up champions tonight?
[03:03.36]It was the night things changed
[03:06.55]Can you see it now?
[03:08.86]When the walls that they put up to hold us back fell down
[03:14.05]It's a revolution, throw your hands up, cause we never gave in
[03:24.05]We'll sing halleluiah
[03:29.05]We'll sing halleluiah
[03:34.86]Hallelujah 
[04:13.80]
