[ar:Taylor Swift]
[ti:Breathe]
[al:Fearless]
[by:Magdi Ali]
[00:00.00]Taylor Swift - Breathe
[00:07.34]Magdi Ali - magdi.a@hotmail.com
[00:10.59]
[00:13.44]I see your face in my mind as I drive away 
[00:20.00]Cause none of us thought it was gonna end that way
[00:26.50]People are people
[00:27.94]And sometimes we change our minds
[00:32.69]But it’s killing me to see you go after all this time
[00:37.88]
[00:39.38]Hmm... Hmm... Hmm...
[00:46.25]Hmm... Hmm... Hmm...
[00:51.07]
[00:52.88]Music starts playing like the end of a sad movie
[00:58.75]It’s the kinda ending you don’t really wanna see
[01:05.12]Cause it’s tragedy and it’ll only bring you down
[01:11.81]Now I don’t know what to be without you around
[01:17.12]
[01:18.18]And we know it’s never simple 
[01:20.61]Never easy 
[01:22.05]Never a clean break, no one here to save me
[01:25.30]You’re the only thing I know like the back of my hand
[01:30.18]And I can’t
[01:31.74]Breathe
[01:35.43]Without you
[01:37.18]But I have to
[01:38.18]Breathe
[01:41.55]Without you
[01:43.11]But I have to...
[01:45.36]
[01:51.06]Never wanted this, never wanna see you hurt
[01:57.43]Every little bump in the road I tried to swerve
[02:03.56]But people are people
[02:05.24]And sometimes it doesn’t work out
[02:10.24]Nothing we say is gonna save us from the fall out
[02:16.62]
[02:17.43]And we know it’s never simple
[02:18.75]Never easy
[02:20.38]Never a clean break, no one here to save me
[02:23.62]You’re the only thing I know like the back of my hand
[02:28.56]And I can’t
[02:30.00]Breathe
[02:33.06]Without you
[02:35.06]But I have to
[02:36.81]Breathe
[02:40.00]Without you
[02:41.44]But I have to...
[02:43.69]
[02:55.66]It’s two A.M.
[02:57.47]Feeling like I just lost a friend
[03:01.29]Hope you know it’s not easy
[03:03.83]Easy for me
[03:08.52]It’s two A.M.
[03:10.27]Feeling like I just lost a friend
[03:14.02]Hope you know this ain’t easy
[03:16.59]Easy for me
[03:20.46]
[03:22.08]And we know it’s never simple
[03:23.79]Never easy
[03:25.35]Never a clean break, no one here to save me
[03:30.20]
[03:30.57]Oh!
[03:33.51]
[03:33.96]I can’t
[03:34.99]Breathe
[03:38.69]Without you
[03:40.07]But I have to
[03:41.69]Breathe
[03:44.82]Without you
[03:46.26]But I have to
[03:48.13]Breathe
[03:51.38]Without you
[03:53.31]But I have to...
[03:56.75]
[04:01.02]Sorry, sorry (Hmm...) 
[04:04.47]Sorry (Eh eh) Sorry (Hmm...)
[04:07.46]Sorry (Eh eh) Sorry (Hmm...)
[04:10.87]Sorry!
[04:13.17]
