[ar:Taylor Swift]
[ti:Fearless]
[al:Fearless]
[by:Magdi Ali]
[00:00.00]Taylor Swift - Fearless
[00:07.34]Magdi Ali - magdi.a@hotmail.com
[00:10.59]
[00:20.55]There's somethin' 'bout the way
[00:22.93]The street looks when it's just rained
[00:25.93]There’s a glow off the pavement
[00:28.62]You walk me to the car
[00:30.55]And you know I wanna ask you to dance right there
[00:35.11]In the middle of the parking lot
[00:38.49]Yeah
[00:43.73]Oh oh
[00:47.05]
[00:49.30]We're drivin' down the road
[00:51.99]I wonder if you know
[00:54.56]I'm tryin' so hard not to get caught up now
[00:58.87]But you're just so cool
[01:01.37]Run your hands through your hair
[01:03.87]Absent mindedly makin' me want you
[01:08.37]
[01:08.74]And I don't know how it gets better than this
[01:13.68]You take my hand and drag me head first
[01:16.76]Fearless
[01:18.12]And I don't know why but with you I'd dance
[01:23.25]In a storm in my best dress
[01:26.25]Fearless
[01:28.94]
[01:37.44]So baby drive slow
[01:39.75]‘Til we run out of road in this one horse town
[01:44.76]I wanna stay right here in this passenger’s seat
[01:49.44]You put your eyes on me
[01:51.88]In this moment now capture every memory
[01:56.38]
[01:56.75]'Cause I don't know how it gets better than this
[02:01.70]You take my hand and drag me head first
[02:04.70]Fearless
[02:06.19]And I don't know why but with you I’d dance
[02:11.19]In a storm in my best dress
[02:14.39]Fearless
[02:16.88]
[02:35.57]Well you stood there with me in the doorway
[02:39.20]My hands shake
[02:40.45]I'm not usually this way but
[02:44.70]You pull me in and I’m a little more brave
[02:48.45]It’s the first kiss, it's flawless, really somethin’ 
[02:55.08]It’s fearless.
[02:59.08]Oh oh oh yeah
[03:05.57]
[03:06.51]'Cause I don't know how it gets better than this
[03:11.21]You take my hand and drag me head first
[03:14.21]Fearless
[03:15.71]And I don't know why but with you I’d dance
[03:20.89]In a storm in my best dress
[03:23.89]Fearless
[03:25.35]
[03:25.72]'Cause I don't know how it gets better than this
[03:30.44]You take my hand and drag me head first
[03:33.50]Fearless
[03:35.06]And I don't know why but with you I’d dance
[03:39.75]In a storm in my best dress
[03:43.19]Fearless
[03:45.96]Oh oh oh yeah
[03:55.04]
